A Guide to the American Lung Association of Virginia (ALAV) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- MEDICAL RESEARCH AND EDUCATION COMMITTEE BY LEWIS CLAYTON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1966-1967, 6-TL,3-JOURN,1-NEWSCLIP,1-pam,9-TLS,3-D,1-ALS (Box-folder 102:008)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION AND RESEARCH COMMITTEE BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: DR. HARRY WALKUP, ET AL., 1962-1963, 7-TL, 7-N, 8-TLS, 9-D, 3-AD (Box-folder 103:001)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION AND RESEARCH COMMITTEE, HAITI AND TUBERCULOSIS BY H. MAC VANDIVIERE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1961-1962, 13-TL,21-TLS,1-C,11-D,2-N,1-NEWSCLIP,1-ALS,2-AD (Box-folder 103:002)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION AND RESEARCH COMMITTEE BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JOHN GUERRET, ET AL., 1960-1961, D-33,TL-30,TLS-27,NS-16,DS-16,N-9 (Box-folder 103:003)
- MEDICAL EDUCATION, CHEST X-RAY, DIAGNOSTIC STANDARDS, CLASSIFICATION OF TUBERCULOSIS BY NATIONAL TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCATION, ET AL., 1937-1941, 4-D (Box-folder 103:004)
- MEDICAL RESEARCH FUND, TUBERCULOSIS VACCINATION BY HAROLD MCGEE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CATHERINE ZAHAROV, ET AL., 1955-1959, 5-TL,7-D,7-TLS,1-N,1-AD (Box-folder 103:005)
- MEDICAL RESEARCH, GRANTS, VACCINE BY JACK GWALTNEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: GORDON MEADE, ET AL., N.D., 14-TLS,13-TL,12-DS,2-JOURN,4-D,1-N (Box-folder 103:006)
- MEDICAL RESEARCH, GRANTS BY HSIU-SHENG HSU, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., N.D., 24-TLS,1-NEWSCLIP, 18-TL,10-DS (Box-folder 103:007)
- MEDICAL RESEARCH, GRANTS BY GORDON MEADE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: SAMI SAID, ET AL., N.D., 13-TL, 13-DS, 4-N, 6-TLS, 6-D (Box-folder 104:001)
- MEDICAL RESEARCH BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: YALE ZIMBERG, ET AL., N.D., 7-TL, 16-TLS, 10-DS, 7-D, 2-N (Box-folder 104:002)
- MEDICAL SOCIETY OF VIRGINIA, EXHIBIT--PRACTICING PHYSICIAN AND TUBERCULOSIS CONTROL, CHEST SURGERY, MEMBERSHIP OF NEGROES, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN HISTORY, SANITORIUMS, COST OF HOSPITALIZATION BY ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: F.A. CULVER, ET AL., 1951-1960, 10-D,9-TL,11-TLS,1-DS,2-N,1-pam,7-NEWSCLIP (Box-folder 104:003)
- MEDICAL SOCIETY OF VIRGINIA, RD DIAGNOSIS AND TREATMENT EXHIBIT, AIR POLLUTION, GUIDE FOR PHYSICIANS TREATING TUBERCULOSIS BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: FRANK BLANTON, ET AL., 1961-1981, 2-N, 14-TL, 9-D, 3-TLS,1-NS (Box-folder 104:004)
- MEDICAL SCHOOLS, TRAINING AT SANATORIUMS BY JOHN BUCHANAN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL., -1949, 5-TLS, 1-N, 2-TL (Box-folder 104:005)
- MEMBERSHIP IN VTA BY SALLYE PUGH, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1955-1961, 1-AD, 2-ALS, 3-TL, 24-D, 5-TLS, 3-N (Box-folder 104:006)
- METROPOLITAN LIFE INSURANCE COMPANY, CHRISTMAS SEAL, FAKE CONSUMPTION CURES, CHANCES FOR REMARRIAGE FOR THE WIDOWED AND DIVORCED BY MEROPOLITAN LIFE INSURANCE COMPANY, ET AL., -1949, 7-TL, 8-TLS, 1-c, 3-D (Box-folder 104:007)
- METROPOLITAN LIFE INSURANCE COMPANY, STATISTICS ON YOUNG MEN, REDUCTION IN CANCER MORTALITY, TRENDS IN HEART DISEASE, POPULATION CHANGES AND HEALTH IMPLICATIONS, MARRIAGES, BABY BOOM ENDING, MOTOR VEHICLE ACCIDENTS BY METROPOLITAN LIFE INSURANCE COMPANY, ET AL., 1962-1967, 1-N, 1-TL, 19-D (Box-folder 104:008)
- METROPOLITAN WASHINGTON COALITION FOR CLEAN AIR BY FRANK JONES, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1970-1974, 6-TLS, 19-D, 9-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 104:009)
- METROPOLITAN WASHINGTON TUBERCULOSIS CONFERENCE, CHEST CLINICS BY ROBER BARRIE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EDWARD FUNKHOUSER, ET AL., 1951-1965, 9-TL, 6-N, 4-c.d.s, 23-D, 11-TLS, 1-AN (Box-folder 105:001)
- METROPOLITAN WASHINGTON CONFERENCES, CHEST X-RAYS BY METROPOLITAN WASHINGTON, ET AL., -1949, 22-D, 4-TL, 8-TLS, 2-c.d.s., 2-c. (Box-folder 105:002)
- MIDDLE ATLANTIC STATES CONFERENCE BY JOHN BATTLE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL., 1952, 15-D, 1-NEWSCLIP, 1-pam, 1-TL, 3-TLS (Box-folder 105:003)
- M GENERAL, LIFE AND BREATH CLINIC, PERFORMANCE REPORT BY CARL BOOBERG, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CHARLES MODJESKI, ET AL., 1979-1980, 2-TLS, 3-TL, 2-RPT, 1-N (Box-folder 105:004)
- NATIONAL TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION ABSTRACTS, RURAL PUBLIC HEALTH, COST AND TREATMENT OF PATIENTS: WRITTEN BY THE NATIONAL TUBERCULOSIS ASSOCIATION, 1928-1971, 93-D (Box-folder 105:005)
- NTA ANNUAL MEETING BY MARK HARRINGTON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: THOMAS PINCKNEY, ET AL., 1953-1954, 4-D, 1-NEWSCLIP, 1-TL, 2-TLS (Box-folder 105:006)
- NTA ANNUAL MEETING, TUBERCULOSIS TESTING BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: DALE KNOTTS, ET AL., 1956-1957, 13-D, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 105:007)
- NTA ANNUAL MEETING, NURSING BY LUCILLE BROWNELL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: R.S. BLACKMEN, ET AL., 1958-1962, 18-TL, 7-D, 5-N, 16-TLS, 4-C, 2-map, 1-pam, 1-c.d.s. (Box-folder 105:008)
- NTA ANNUAL MEETING BY JAMES PERKINS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1962-1963, 19-TLS, 14-TL, 14-D, 9-N, 2-map, 1-AD, 3-pam (Box-folder 105:009)
- NTA ANNUAL MEETING BY NTA, ET AL., 1963-1964, 3-pam, 16-D, 6-N, 2-TLS, 5-TL (Box-folder 106:001)
- NTA ANNUAL MEETING BY NTA, 1965-1966, 2-TL, 1-TLS, 4-D (Box-folder 106:002)
- NTA ANNUAL MEETING BY NTA, 1966-1967, 1-ANS, 1-TLS, 8-D, 1-pam (Box-folder 106:003)
- NTRDA ANNUAL MEETING BY NTRDA, ET AL., 1968-1969, 8-D, 5-pam, 1-TL (Box-folder 106:004)
- NTA ANNUAL MEETING BY NTA, ET AL, 1967-1968, 2-D, 1-TLS, 4-N (Box-folder 106:005)
- NTRDA ANNUAL MEETING BY NTRDA, ET AL, 1969-1971, 7-N, 4-TL, 2-TLS, 1-AN, 1-photo, 6-D (Box-folder 106:006)
- NTRDA ANNUAL MEETING BY NTRDA, ET AL., 1971-1973, 8-TL, 2-TLS, 4-DS, 7-D (Box-folder 106:007)
- ALA ADULT LUNG DISEASE COMMITTEE BY CARL BOOBERG, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: GEORGE WOOD, ET AL., 1979-1980, 1-D, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 107:001)
- ALA ANNUAL MEETING BY ALA, ET AL, 1973-1974, 1-pam, 6-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 107:002)
- ALA ANNUAL MEETING BY ALA, ET AL., 1974-1976, 7-D, 3-DS, 1-pam, 1-TLS, 2-TL, 1-N (Box-folder 107:003)
- ALA ANNUAL MEETING BY ALA, ET AL., 1976-1977, 5-D, 3-TL, 1-TLS, 2-N (Box-folder 107:004)
- ALA ANNUAL REPORT BY ALA, ET AL, 1977-1978, 23-D, 9-TL, 4-TLS, 1-N, 1-AD (Box-folder 107:005)
- ALA ANNUAL MEETING BY ALA, ET AL, 1978-1980, 14-D, 3-TL, 9-N, 1-TLS, 1-DS (Box-folder 107:006)
- ALA ANNUAL MEETING BY ALA, ET AL., 1980-1981, 6-D, 2-TL (Box-folder 107:007)
- ALA ANNUAL REPORTS BY ALA, 1973-1975, 2-D (Box-folder 107:008)
- ALA ANNUAL REPORTS BY ALA, ET AL., 1975-1976, 5-D, 1-TL, 1-N (Box-folder 107:012)
- ALA ANNUAL REPORTS BY ALA, ET AL., 1976-1977, 4-D, 1-DS (Box-folder 107:009)
- ALA ANNUAL REPORTS BY ALA, ET AL., 1977-1979, 4-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 107:010)
- ALA ANNUAL REPORTS BY ALA, 1979-1981, 4-D (Box-folder 107:011)
- NTA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTA, 1948-1951, 2-D (Box-folder 108:001)
- NTA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTA, 1951-1953, 2-D (Box-folder 108:002)
- NTA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTA, 1957-1959, 2-D (Box-folder 108:003)
- NTA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTA, 1961-1963, 2-D (Box-folder 108:004)
- NTA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTA, ET AL, 1961-1962, 4-D, 1-AD, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 108:005)
- NTA ANNUAL REPORT BY NTA, ET AL., 1963-1965, 3-D, 1-ANS, 1-TLS (Box-folder 108:006)
- NTA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTA, ET AL., 1965-1968, 4-D, 1-N (Box-folder 108:007)
- NTRDA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTRDA, ET AL., 1968-1970, 3-N, 3-D (Box-folder 108:008)
- NTRDA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTRDA, 1970-1972, 3-D (Box-folder 108:009)
- NTRDA ANNUAL REPORTS BY NTRDA, ET AL, 1972-1973, 1-D, 1-N (Box-folder 108:010)
- NTA ARCHIVES, DR. PHILIP JACOBS, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH, HERMANN BIGGS, N.D., 5-D, 3-NEWSCLIP, 1-TLS (Box-folder 109:001)
- NTA ARDEN HOUSE CONFERENCE, STATISTICS FOR TUBERCULOSIS CASES, BLACK/AFRICAN AMERICAN PUBLIC HEALTH, SOCIO-ECONOMICS OF TUBERCULOSIS CASES, NON-HOSPITALIZED PATIENTS BY U.S. DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, EDUCATION, AND WELFARE, 1959, 9-D, 3-TL, 2-N (Box-folder 109:002)
- ALA BOARD OF DIRECTORS,MEETING MINUTES BY RICHARD SINSHEIMER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALA BOARD, ET AL., 1980-1981, 13-D, 5-N, 1-NEWSCLIP, 5-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 109:003)
- ALA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY GORDON BECK, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1979-1980, 37-D, 1-ALS, 1-N, 1-TL, 1-TLS, 1-pam (Box-folder 109:004)
- ALA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY RICHARD SINSHEIMER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1978-1979, 87-D, 20-N, 3-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 109:005)
- PUBLICATIONS BY VIRGINIA DABNEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: REMINGONT RAND, ET AL., 1968-1969, 2-TL, 15-N, 1-AN, 7-D, 1-pam (Box-folder 109:002)
- ALA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY JAMES KIERAN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1976-1978, 11-D, 3-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 110:001)
- ALA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY JOSEPTH STOCKLEN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1975-1976, 1-DS, 3-N, 2-TLS, 7-D, 3-TL (Box-folder 110:002)
- ALA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY JOSEPH STOCKLEN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1974-1975, 28-D, 1-N, 4-TL, 1-DS (Box-folder 110:003)
- ALA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORT BY JAY NADEL, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1973-1974, 13-D, 3-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 110:004)
- NTRDA BOARD OF DIRECTORS,MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY JOHN C. HARRISON, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1971-1973, 10-D, 2-TLS, 3-N (Box-folder 110:005)
- NTRDA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY WILLIAM TUCKER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1970-1971, 26-D, 2-N, 1-TLS, 1-TL (Box-folder 110:006)
- NTRDA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY JOHN GOMPERTZ, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1968-1970, 8-D, 5-TLS, 3-TL (Box-folder 110:007)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY SYDNEY JACOBS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTOR, ET AL., 1966-1968, 11-D, 2-TL (Box-folder 111:001)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORTS BY WILLIAM COOKE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1964-1966, 9-D, 3-TL (Box-folder 111:002)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORT BY PETER JANSS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS ET AL., 1963-1964, 11-D, 3-TLS, 7-N, 2-TL, 2-AN (Box-folder 111:003)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS BY ROBERT RAGSDALE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1962-1963, 5-D, 1-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 111:004)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORT/ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1961-1962, 6-D, 3-TL, 1-N, 1-TLS (Box-folder 111:005)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORT/ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1960-1961, 5-NEWSCLIPS, 2-TLS, 5-D, 3-N, 3-TL (Box-folder 111:006)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORT BY H. MCLEOD RIGGINS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1958-1960, 6-TL, 8-D, 4-TLS, 2-N (Box-folder 111:007)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORT BY JULES SCHNEIDER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1956-1958, 8-D, 1-TLS, 4-TL, 6-N (Box-folder 111:008)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS BY ESMOND LONG, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALTON POPE, ET AL., 1955-1956, 6-TL, 5-D, 2-TLS (Box-folder 111:009)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORT/ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1954-1955, 8-D, 1-TLS, 2-N (Box-folder 111:010)
- NTA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, MEETING MINUTES, REPORT/ADDRESSED TO: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1951-1953, 3-N, 7-D (Box-folder 111:011)
- ALA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY ALA, 1975-1976, 1-D (Box-folder 112:001)
- ALA BUDGET AND FINNANCIAL BY ALA, 1974-1975, 1-N, 1-D (Box-folder 112:002)
- NTRDA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY NTRDA, 1972-1973, 1-D (Box-folder 112:003)
- NTRDA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY NTRDA, 1970-1971, 1-D, 1-N (Box-folder 112:004)
- NTRDA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY NTRDA, 1969-1970, 1-D (Box-folder 112:005)
- NTRDA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY NTRDA, 1968-1969, 1-D (Box-folder 112:006)
- NTA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY NTA, 1967-1968, 1-D (Box-folder 112:007)
- NTA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY NTA, 1964-1967, 2-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 112:008)
- NTA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY NTA, 1963-1964, 3-D (Box-folder 112:009)
- VTA AND NTA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORTS BY VTA, NTA, 1952-1953, 12-D, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 112:010)
- NTA FINANCIAL REPORTS BY NTA, 1950-1951, 1-AN, 10-N, 13-TL, 12-D, 10-TLS, 4-DS (Box-folder 113:001)
- VTA END OF THE YEAR REPORTS, NTA BUDGET AND FINANCIAL BY VTA, NTA, 1943-1944, 28-D, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 113:002)
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, ET AL., 1980-1981, 7-D, 1-TLS, 3-TL (Box-folder 113:003)
  CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, ET AL., 1980-1981, 12-D, 1-N, 3-TL (Box-folder 113:004)
  ASTHMA, PATIENT EDUCATION, SECOND HAND SMOKE
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, 1979-1980, 11-D (Box-folder 113:005)
  CLEAN AIR, HISTORY OF TUBERCULOSIS TREATMENT
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, 1978-1979, 10-D, 2-TL, 2-TLS (Box-folder 113:006)
  NURSING, SMOKING IN WORKPLACE, INFLUENZA, CLEAN AIR
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, 1977-1978, 17-D, 1-TLS, 12-TL, 1-N (Box-folder 113:007)
  NATIVE AMERICAN/INDIAN PUBLIC HEALTH, PUBLIC HEALTH CARE AT HOME, ATTITUDES TOWARD SMOKING, HEALTH EDUCATION
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, 1976-1977, 10-D (Box-folder 113:008)
  NON-SMOKER'S RIGHTS, HEALTH EDUCATION, ASTHMA
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, 1975-1976, 10-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 114:001)
  NURSING, CLEAN AIR
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, ET AL., 1974-1975, 11-D, 2-TL, 2-TLS (Box-folder 114:002)
  CHRISTMAS SEAL SALES, CLEAN AIR, NURSING
- ALA BULLETIN BY ALA, 1973-1974, 10-D (Box-folder 114:003)
  PUBLIC HEALTH CARE, CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE, MEXICAN AMERICAN AND PUBLIC HEALTH
- NTRDA BULLETIN BY NTRDA, ET AL., 1972-1973, 1-TLS, 12-D (Box-folder 114:004)
  CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE, SANATORIUMS, CLEAN AIR
- NTRDA BULLETIN BY NTRDA, 1971-1972, 17-D (Box-folder 114:005)
  PUBLIC HEALTH CARE, NURSING, CHEST X-RAYS
- NTRDA BULLETIN BY NTRDA, ET AL., 1970-1971, 13-D, 1-NS (Box-folder 114:006)
  VIRGINIA YOUTH, CHILDREN AND SMOKING, PUBLIC HEALTH CARE
- NTRDA BULLETIN BY NTRDA, 1969-1970, 12-D (Box-folder 114:007)
  SANATORIUMS, PUBLIC HEALTH CARE, MEDICAL EDUCATION, STATISTICS FOR TUBERCULOSIS CASES, CLEAN AIR
- NTRDA BULLETIN BY NTRDA, 1968-1969, 12-D (Box-folder 114:008)
  POOR AND PUBLIC HEALTH, CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE, CLINICS
- NTA BULLETIN BY NTA, 1967-1968, 10-D, 1-TLS, 1-TL (Box-folder 114:009)
  CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE, PUBLIC HEALTH CARE, CLEAN AIR
- NTA BULLETIN BY NTA, 1966-1967, 13-D, 2-TL, 2-TLS (Box-folder 114:010)
  CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE, CLEAN AIR, PUBLIC HEALTH CARE
- NTA BULLETIN BY NTA, 1965-1966, 13-D (Box-folder 115:001)
  POOR AND PUBLIC HEALTH, VOLUNTEERS, TUBERCULIN TESTING, CLEAN AIR
- NTA BULLETIN BY NTA, 1964-1965, 7-D, 1-AD, 1-TL, 4-TLS (Box-folder 115:002)
- NTA BULLETIN BY NTA, 1963-1964, 8-D (Box-folder 115:003)
  CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE, CLINICS
- NTA BULLETIN BY NTA, ET AL., 1958-1963, 1-AN, 5-TLS, 5-TL (Box-folder 115:004)
- ALA BUSINESS OPERATIONS BY DAVID KUSKIN, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALA MEMBERS, ET AL., 1976-1979, 1-N, 1-TLS, 1-TL, 2-D, 1-AD (Box-folder 115:005)
- NTA CHRISTMAS SEAL HONORARY CHAIRMAN BY NTA, 1961, 1-D, 2-photos (Box-folder 115:006)
- ALA CALANDER, 1978-1979, 1-D (Box-folder 115:007)
- NTRDA CHRISTMAS SEAL CAMPAIGN, 1968-1970, 2-D, 2-TL (Box-folder 115:008)
- NTA CHRISTMAS SEAL CAMPAIGN BY R.G. SKETCHLEY JR., ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HARRIET L. REMINGTON, 1965-1968, 10-TL, 17-TLS, 4-N, 1-c., 17-D (Box-folder 115:009)
- NTA CHRISTMAS SEAL SALES BY NELSON KRAEMER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL., 1949-1950, 17-D, 16-TL, 8-N, 10-TLS, 1-c. (Box-folder 115:010)
  PROMOTIONAL MILK BOTTLE COLLAR
- ALA CLINCIAL NOTES, 1980-1981, 2-TLS, 2-TL, 8-D, 1-N (Box-folder 115:011)
- ALA CLINCIAL PROJECT BY NTA, 1966-1969, 1-N, 6-D, 6-TLS, 2-TL (Box-folder 115:012)
  OUTPATIENT RESEARCH
- ALA COMMITTEE ON CONSTITUENT RELATIONS, FORMERLY Q AND C BY ALICE PORTER, PRISCILLA STEELE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CONSTITUENT EXECUTIVES AND PRESIDENTS, ET AL, 1979-1980, 6-N, 19-D, 1-ANS, 5-TL, 1-pam, 1-TLS (Box-folder 116:001)
- ALA COMMITTEE ON CONSTITUENT RELATIONS, FORMERLY Q AND C BY TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALICE PORTER, ET AL., 1978-1979, 20-D, 6-N, 1-pam, 5-TL (Box-folder 116:002)
- ALA COMMITTEE ON CONSTITUENT RELATIONS, FORMERLY Q AND C BY ALICE PORTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL, 1977-1978, 1-DS, 2-AN, 1-pam, 17-D, 4-N, 1-TLS (Box-folder 116:003)
- ALA COMMITTEE ON CONSTITUENT RELATIONS, FORMERLY Q AND C BY HELEN OSTWALD, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1976-1977, 3-TLS, 2-TL, 2-N, 16-D, 1-pam (Box-folder 116:004)
- ALA COMMITTEE ON CONSTITUENT RELATIONS BY ALICE PORTER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CONSTITUENT ASSOCIATIONS, ET AL., 1975-1976, 1-AD, 12-D, 1-TL, 4-N, 1-TLS, 1-pam (Box-folder 116:005)
- ALA COMMITTEE ON CONSTITUENT RELATIONS BY LOUISE BAGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALICE PORTER, ET AL., 1974-1975, 1-AD, 1-TL, 4-N, 22-D, 1-DS (Box-folder 116:006)
- ALA COMMITTEE ON CONSTITUENT RELATIONS BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALICE PORTER, ET AL., 1973-1974, 1-DS, 27-D, 3-N, 4-TL, 2-TLS (Box-folder 116:007)
- NTRDA QUALIFICATIONS AND CONTRACT BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EUGENE HUGHES, ET AL., 1972-1973, 32-D, 2-N, 2-TLS, 2-TL, 6-DS, 2-AD (Box-folder 117:001)
- NTRDA QUALIFICATIONS AND CONTRACT BY LOUISE BAGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALICE PORTER, ET AL., 1970-1972, 24-D, 2-TLS, 2-TL, 2-N, 1-D (Box-folder 117:002)
- NTRDA COMMITTEE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND RESEARCH BY JOHN GOMPERTZ, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL, 1968-1969, 1-D, 1-TLS (Box-folder 117:003)
- NTA CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE CONSULTATION BY CLARENCE KEHOE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W.W WENDT, ET AL., 1958-1959, 2-D, 2-TLS, 2-c. (Box-folder 117:004)
- NTA CONSULTATION BY DOROTHY MICALE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL., 1954-1956, 10-D, 3-TLS, 2-TL (Box-folder 117:005)
- CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE NTA CONSULTATION BY CLARENCE KEHOE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL., 1952-1953, 9-D, 2-AD, 10-TL, 5-TLS, 1-N (Box-folder 117:006)
- NTA CHRISTMAS SEAL CAMPAIGN COST STUDY CLUB BY NTA, 1967-1968, 3-D, 1-N, 4-TL (Box-folder 117:007)
- NTA CHRISTMAS SEAL SALE DEMONSTRATION BY ROBERT BARRIE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: WALTER JAMES, ET AL., 1951-1954, 12-TL, 12-D, 5-TLS, 2-N (Box-folder 117:008)
- NTA COLLECTOR'S SERVICE BY CHARLES LORENZ, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: NANCY LUTZ, ET AL., 1952-1953, 2-D, 1-TLS, 1-TL (Box-folder 117:009)
  INCLUDES 1952 CHRISTMAS SEALS
- NTRDA COMMITTEE ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND RESEARCH BY NTRDA, 1972-1973, 1-N, 1-D (Box-folder 117:010)
- NTRDA COMMITTEE ON PROFESSIONAL EDUCATION AND RESEARCH BY NTRDA, 1970-1971, 3-D, 1-N (Box-folder 117:011)
- NTA COMMITTEE ON QUALIFICATIONS BY JAMES STONE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: LESLIE FOSTER, ET AL., -1949, 30-TLS, 1-journ, 3-DS, 12-TL, 20-D, 1-ALS (Box-folder 117:012)
- NTA COMMITTEE ON REV. OF AUTHORIZED FORMS OF TB WORK BY THOMAS PICKNEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: WILLIAM COOKE, ET AL., 1955-1956, 1-N, 1-TL (Box-folder 117:013)
- NTA COMMUNICATIONS COMMITTEE BY NTA, 1967-1968, 1-N (Box-folder 117:014)
- ALA COMMUNICATIONS SERVICE AUDIO-VISUAL BY ALA, ET AL., 1977-1980, 4-D, 2-N, 1-ANS, 1-TL, 1-TLS (Box-folder 118:001)
  ROX...SOX...NOX...A FILM ON THE ANATOMY OF AIR POLLUTION
- ALA COMMUNICATIONS SERVICE, PUBLIC RELATIONS BY HELEN JONES, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CATHERINE WELTON, ET AL, 1977-1981, 3-TLS, 3-TLS, 3-D (Box-folder 118:002)
- ALA COMMUNICATIONS SERVICE, PUBLIC RELATIONS BY HUGH CLARK, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: RICHARD RUDDELL, ET AL., 1976-1979, 1-ALS,2-DS,3-N,2-TLS,10-TL,3-D (Box-folder 118:003)
- ALA COMMUNICATIONS SERVICE, MATERIALS DEVELOPMENT BY VIRGINIA DABNEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ED SIERKS, ET AL., 1976-1981, 4-D, 2-N, 10-TLS, 7-TL (Box-folder 118:004)
- ALA CONFERENCE OF STATE EXECUTIVES BY TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: HOTEL ROYAL PLAZA, ET AL., 1980-1981, 1-pam, 1-N, 1-TL, 6-D (Box-folder 118:005)
- ALA CONFERENCE OF STATE EXECUTIVES BY ROBERT RAGSDALE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EXECUTIVES OF CONSTITUENT ASSOCIATIONS,ET AL., 1976-1980, 2-pam, 9-N, 1-TLS, 10-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 118:006)
- ALA CONFERENCE OF STATE EXECUTIVES BY W.W. WENDT, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROBERT RAGSDALE, ET AL., 1975-1976, 2-pam, 4-N, 1-TL, 3-D (Box-folder 118:007)
- ALA CONFERENCE OF STATE EXECUTIVES BY ROBERT RAGSDALE, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: GERALD RISO, ET AL., 1974-1975, 1-TLS, 4-N, 2-pam, 5-D, 1-DS, 1-TL, 1-AD (Box-folder 118:008)
- ALA CONFERENCE OF STATE EXECUTIVES BY R.G. SKETCHLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: DONALD KUHN, ET AL, 1973-1974, 1-pam, 3-D, 6-TL, 1-c.d.s., 3-DS, 6-N, 1-TLS (Box-folder 118:009)
- NTRDA CONFERENCE OF STATE EXECUTIVES BY KEN LANGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: STATE EXECUTIVES, ET AL., 1969-1972, 7-D, 2-TL, 3-N (Box-folder 118:010)
- ALA CONTRACT BY ROBERT WEYMUELLER, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ALA BOARD OF DIRECTORS, ET AL., 1979-1981, 4-N, 1-TL, 1-TLS, 9-D (Box-folder 118:011)
- ALA CONTRACT BY LOUISE BAGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: GERALD RISO, ET AL., 1975-1978, 5-TL, 1-TLS, 7-N, 9-D (Box-folder 118:012)
- ALA CONTRACT BY ALA, 1973-1975, 2-D (Box-folder 118:013)
- NTRDA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, END OF THE YEAR REPORT BY F. W. CAPPER,ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: L. MANNING BURCHER, ET AL., 1972-1973, 2-DS, 1-D, 1-TL (Box-folder 118:014)
- NTRDA CONTRACT BY ALA, 1969-1972, 4-DS, 3-TL, 1-N (Box-folder 118:015)
- NTA CONTRACT BY LOUISE BAGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JAMES PERKINS, ET AL., 1965-1967, 4-N, 2-TL, 2-D, 3-DS, 1-AD (Box-folder 118:016)
- NTA CONTRACT BY LOUISE BAGLEY, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: JAMES PERKINS, ET AL., 1963-1965, 1-DS, 1-TL, 1-N, 1-TLS, 1-D (Box-folder 118:017)
- NTA CONTRACT BY NTA, 1959-1963, 7-DS, 3-N, 4-TL, 1-AD, 1-D, 1-TLS (Box-folder 118:018)
- NTA CONTRACT BY JAMES PERKINS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: W.W. WENDT, ET AL., 1955-1959, 1-TLS, 4-DS, 2-D, 2-N, 3-TL (Box-folder 118:019)
- CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL STATEMENTS BY NTA, 1954-1955, 3-D (Box-folder 119:001)
- NTA CONTRACT CHANGES BY EMMET MATTHEWS, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE, ET AL., 1953-1954, 4-D, 1-N, 1-NS, 1-TL (Box-folder 119:002)
- NTRDA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTRDA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1964-1972, 8-D, 3-DS (Box-folder 119:003)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTRDA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1963-1964, 1-DS, 1-TL, 1-N, 1-pam, 51-D (Box-folder 119:004)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1962-1963, 2-N, 30-D (Box-folder 119:005)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1961-1962, 1-TL, 2-TLS, 1-DS, 1-N, 11-D (Box-folder 119:006)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1960-1961, 3-TL, 2-TLS, 2-DS, 15-D (Box-folder 119:007)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1959-1960, 4-DS, 2-TLS, 11-D (Box-folder 119:008)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1958-1959, 1-TLS, 1-AD, 2-TL, 1-N, 14-D (Box-folder 119:009)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1951-1958, 2-DS, 2-TL, 2-TLS, 13-D (Box-folder 119:010)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1956-1957, 2-TL, 2-TLS, 16-D (Box-folder 119:011)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1955-1956, 2-N, 3-TLS, 4-TL, 26-D (Box-folder 119:012)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1954-1955, 1-map, 3-TLS, 2-TL, 2-N, 32-D (Box-folder 119:013)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL, YEAR END REPORT BY VTA/ADDRESSED TO: NTA, 1953-1954, 1-TL, 1-map, 20-D (Box-folder 119:014)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL STATEMENTS BY VTA, 1953-1954, 2-N, 2-TLS, 1-AD, 7-D (Box-folder 120:001)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANCIAL STATEMENTS BY VTA, 1952-1953, 3-N, 5-TL, 4-TLS, 1-AD, 6-D (Box-folder 120:002)
- NTA CONTRACT AND FINANACIAL STATEMENTS BY VTA, 1951-1952, 2-TL, 1-TLS, 2-N, 18-D (Box-folder 120:003)
- ALA CONTROLLER'S OFFICE BY ANTHONY OZELLO, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: CONSTITUENT AND AFFILIATE ASSOCIATION, ET AL., 1980-1981, 4-NS, 4-D, 3-TLS, 1-TL (Box-folder 120:004)
- ALA CONTROLLER'S OFFICE BY ANTHONY OZELLO, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: VLA, 1978-1979, 1-DS, 1-D (Box-folder 120:005)
- ALA CONTROLLER'S OFFICE BY TAYLOR COPPING, ET AL./ADDRESSED TO: ROD LADOUSIER, ET AL., 1977-1978, 2-TL, 1-DS, 1-N, 9-D, 1-TLS (Box-folder 120:006)